Finding Aid for the William Campbell Binkley Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- 1 roll of microfilm, unidentified (Box 40 (7))
BROWN, B. F. (North Carolina State College) - 1 (Aug. 26, 1942)
BROWN, B. June - 1 (July 26, 1959)
BROWN, C. A. (Birmingham Board of Education) - 1 (Feb. 1, 1937)
BROWN, J. Douglas (Princeton University) - 2 (1959)
BROWN, Lula L. - 3 (1931, 1932)
BROWN, Norman (University of Texas) - 1 (Sept. 20, 1963)
BROWN, W. Burlie - 2 (1954, n.d.) (including 1 from Stephens Rice)
BROWNE, A. D. - 3 (1939.41)
BROWNING, Gordon (Tennessee Executive Chamber) - 1 (Mar. 27, 1950)
BROWNING, Howard M. - 9 (1937, 1940, 1941, 1943, 1945)
BROWNING, Leo H. (Middle Georgia College) - 1 (Feb. 5, 1936)
BRUCE, E. L. Company. (E.L. Fellman) - 1 (Sept. 5, 1945)
BRUCE, Harold L. (University of California) - 2 (1930)
BRUCE, Kathleen (Sophie Newcomb College) - 5 (1944)
BRYAN, J. M. (Missouri Pacific Lines) - 1 (June 1, 1932)
BUCK, Solon J. (American Historical Association Endowment Fund) - 1 (Aug. 10, 1926)
BUCK, Vera H. (Albion College) - 2 (1939)
BUDD, Edward - 1 (Aug. 13, 1940)
BULL, H. D. (Prince George Parish, Winyah) - 2 (1943, 1946)
BULTMAN, William A. (Arkansas State Teachers College) - 1 (Apr. 12, 1946)
BUNCH, Marion E. (Washington University) - 1 (Dec. 17, 1962)
BURK, J. E. (Ward-Belmont) - 1 (July 28, 1942)
BURNETT, Edmund C. (Carnegie Institution) - 3 (1942)
BURNETTE, Lawrence Jr. (State Historical Society of Wisconsin) - 2 (1961) (including 1 from Frances G. James)
BURT, Jesse C., Jr. (Florence State Teachers College, Lambuth College) -33 (1946-49, 1951, 1952, 1954-56) (including letters to J.C.B. from George W. Stocking, Milbrey W. Miller, and Dan M. Robison)
BURTON, L. Dortch - 1 (May 11, 1942)
BURTS, Robert M., Jr. - 1 (July 13, 1953)
BUTCHER, H. Borton - 1 (Apr. 14, 1928)
BUTTS, A. B. (Mississippi State College) - 1 (Mar. 13, 1935)
BYERLY, Kenneth - 1 (Feb. 23, 1934)
CALDWELL, Roy H. - 1 (Feb. 6, 1922)
CALHOUN, J. W. (University of Texas) - 3 (1938, 1939)
CALLAHAN, North - 1 (Nov. 25, 1949)
CALLCOTT, W. H. (University of South Carolina) - 2 (1931, 1947)
CALVERT, Kae Venable - 22 (1953, 1956-59, 1963, 1965, 1969) (including 1 letter each from W.R. Hogan and R.M. Lumiansky)
CAMARA CASCUDO, Luis da (Sociedade Brasileira de Folk-Lore) - 1 (Dec. 23, 1943)
CAMPBELL, Adele - 1 (July 10, 1927)
CAMPBELL, Mary R. - 6 (1936-39)
CANNON, M. Hamlin (National Archives) - 1 (Apr. 1, 1945)
CANTWELL, J. W. (Oklahoma A. and M. College) - 3 (1920)
CAPERS, Charlotte (Mississippi Department of Archives and History) - 2 (1943)
CAPERS, Gerald M. (Yale University, Newcomb College) - 5 (1938, 1939, 1947)
CAPPON, Lester J. (University of Virginia, Institute of Early American History and Culture, Southern Historical Association) - 28 (1944, 1947-51)
CARMICUAEL, O.C. (Vanderbilt University) - 8 (1936, 1937, 1940, 1942, 1943, 1945)
CARPENTER, L. G. (Consulting Engineer) - 1 (Mar. 26, 1927)
CARR, Minnie Pearl (Colorado Education Association) - 2 (1923)
CARROLL, E. Malcolm (Duke University) - 2 (1954)
CARROON, Frank (New Mexico Normal University) - 1 (Nov. 9, 1928)
CARSON, George Barr Jr. (Service Center for Teachers of History) - 2 (1957)
CARSON, Jane (Newcomb College) - 1 (Feb. 1, 1950)
CARTER, Clarence E. (Miami University, Territorial Papers, National Archives) - 37 (1925, 1933-37, 1939, 1942-45, 1947, 1951)
CARTER, Harvey L. (Colorado College) - 3 (1963)
CARTER, Purvis M. (Prairie View A & M College) - 1 (Nov. 22, 1965)
CARNRIGHT, Morse A. (University of California Press) - 1 (Sept. 26, 1925)
CASAGRANDE, Joseph B. (Social Science Research Council) - 1 (June 14, 1950)
CASKEY, W. M. (Peabody College, Vanderbilt University, Louisiana State University, Mississippi College) - 16 (1931-36, 1953)
CASSELL, Robert (Works Progress Administration) - 1 (Feb. 6, 1940)
CASSLES, Ethel - 1 (Aug. 11, 1921)
CASTLE, Catherine (Peabody College) - 1 (Mar. 16, 1938)
CASWELL, Ruth A. (Columbia University) - 2 (1941, 1942)
GATES, Thelma (State Teachers College, Troy) - 1 (Feb. 19, 1948)
CAUGHEY, John (University of California, Pacific Historical Review) - 4 (1946, 1948, 1951, 1964)
CAYWOOD, Bruce P. - 7 (1931, 1932)
CHAFFIN, Nora C. (Duke University, Vanderbilt University) - 14 (1944-46, 1948-52)
CHAN, Helen (Appleton-Century-Crofts) - 1 (June 24, 1963)
CHAPMAN, Charles E. (University of California) - 2 (1920, 1925)
CHAPPELL, Gordon T. (Winthrop College, Newberry College, Huntington College) - 28 (1938-42, 1945, 1950, 1951, 1953, 1956)
CHARVAT, William (Ohio State) - 1 (Nov. 1, 1948)
CHENEY, Frances Neel (Peabody Library School) - 2 (1945, 1951)
CHERRINGTON, Ernest H., Jr. (Centenary College of Louisiana) - 1 (Aug. 5, 1946)
CHILDS, St. Julien Ravenel (Brooklyn College) - 1 (Jan. 21, 1943)
CHITWOOD, O. P. (West Virginia University) - 3 (1943, n.d.)
CHOATE, J. E. Jr. (David Lipscomb College) - 1 (Oct. 27, 1955)
CHRISTIAN, A. K. (University of Oklahoma) - 5 (1922, 1923, 1925, 1927, 1939)
CLARK, Charles B. (Washington College) - 1 (Nov. 23, 1936)
CLARK, Emily (Newcomb College) - 1 (Jan. l8, 1969)
CLARK, Elmer T. (World Outlook) - 1 (July 19, 1951)
CLARK, J. L. (Sam Houston State Teachers College) - 2 (1937)
CLARK, John B. (Lincoln Memorial University) - 1 (Oct. 7, 1947)
CLARK, Thomas D. (University of Kentucky, Jouxtnal of Southern History, Mississippi Valley Historical Association, Organization of American Historians) - ll8 (1931, 1938, 1939, 1941-53, 1958-62, 1970)
CLARKE, Mary W. - 5 (1966)
CLARKE, W. P. - 8 (1922, 1926, 1927, 1929, 1937, 1940, 1941)
CLARKSON, Jesse D. (Brooklyn College) - 2 (1942)
CLARKSON, R. E. - 1 (Jan. 11, 1938)
CLEETON, GLEN U. (Carnegie Institute of Technology) - 1 (June 7, 1948)
CLELAND, J. S. (Monmouth College) - 1 (July 26, 1947)
CLEM, Orlie M. (Public Schools of Owego, N.Y.) - 1 (Sept. 20, 1935)
CLEMEN, Rudolf A. (Society of American Historians) - 2 (l946, 1950)
CLEVEN, N. Andrew N. (University of Arkansas) - 1 (Mar. 27, 1921)
CLEVENGER, Homer (Lindenwood College) - 1 (May 22, 1944)
CLIFTON, Frances - see F. C. Daniels
CLINE, Phil - 1 (n.d.)
CLYDE, Paul H. (Duke University) - 1 (Nov. 23, 1949)
COAN, Charles F. (State University of New Mexico) - 30 (1920-27)
COCKING, Walter D. (Tennessee Department of Education) - 2 (1933, 1935)
COEN, B. F. (Colorado State Agricultural College) - 3 (1927, 1928)
COLE, Arthur C. (Mississippi Valley Historical Review, Brooklyn College) - 31 (1935-40, 1952) (includes letters from Richard R. Stenberg)
COLE, Fred. C. (Jonrnal of Southern History, Department of the Navy, Tulane University, Mississippi Valley Historical Review) - 47 (1936, 1939-43, 1945-47, 1949, 1951-53, 1959) (including letters from Robert Love, Russell Nichol, and Howard E. Baughman)
COLE, Lois Dwight (G.P. Putnam's Sons) - 1 (Aug. 7, 1958)
COLEMAN, Herbert E. - 3 (1944)
COLEMAN, R. V. (Atlas of American History, Dictionary of American History) - 2 (1938, 1941)
COLES, Harry L., Jr. (National Archives, Ohio State University, Naval War College) - 45 (1942-51, 1953, 1957, 1960-62, 1966)
COLES, J. William (First American National Bank) - 1 (Sept. 30, 1953)
COLES, Pat - 1 (n.d.)
COLLIER, P.F. & Sons - 2 (1934)
COLLINS, Alan C. (Doubleday, Doran and Co.) - 3 (1933)
COMETTI, Elizabeth (Marshall College) - 1 (Jan. 20, 1950)
CONEY, Donald (University of Texas Library) - 2 (1937)
CONKIN, Paul K. - 2 (1955, 1964)
COOK, R. C. - 1 (Nov. 6, 1951)
COPE, Helene Robbins - 7 (1962) (including letters from John P. Dyer and J.C. Morris)
COPELAND, J. Isaac (Peabody College Library) - 1 (Nov. 3, 1966)
CORBITT, Duvon C. (University of Omaha) - 1 (July 31, 1945)
COTNER, R. C. (University of Texas) - 4 (1951, 1952, 1963)
COTTERILL, Robert S. (Fla State College for Women, Southern Historical Association, Florida State University) - 6 (1943, 1944, 1946, 1948, 1950)
COUCH, William T. (University of North Carolina Press, Works Progress Administration) - 19 (1933, 1938, 1940, 1942) (including letters from Mary T. Bobbitt, A.Y. Lloyd, and Mary T. Littlejohn)
COULTER, E. Merton (University of Georgia, Louisiana State University, University of Kentucky, University of Texas, Southern Historical Association) - 47 (1922-25, 1928, 1931, 1932, 1935, 1938, 1942, 1943, 1945, 1946, 1948, 1949, 1951) (including letters from Benjamin B. Kendrick and A.M. Shaw, Jr.)
COUSINS, Paul M. (Shorter College) - 1 (May 17, 1946)
COVER, John H. (University of Denver) - 1 (May 13, 1927)
COWEN, D. D. (American National Bank) - 1 (Jan. 11, 1940)
COX, Isaac J. (Northwestern University, Louisiana State University) - 9 (1931, 1933, 1936, 1938, 1939, 1941, 1943)
COX, LaWanda (Dartmouth College, Hunter College, City College of New York) - 3 (19V7, 1948, 1963)
COZENS, Frederick W. (University of California) - 1 (Apr. 2, 1925)
CRADDOCK, John W. - 1 (Feb. 5, 1943)
CRAMER, J. H. - 1 (Oct. 25, 1945)
CRANE, Robert T. (Social Science Research Council) - 1 (Feb. 20, 1953)
CRAVEN, Avery O. (University of Chicago) - 4 (1939, 1948, 1949)
CRAVEN, Wesley Frank (New York University, Princeton University) - 9 (1942, 1943, 1946, 1955)
CRAWFORD, Meredith P. (Vanderbilt University) - 4 (1949)
CRESAP, Bernarr (Florence State College) - 13 (1947, 1950, 1953, 1954, 1956, 1959, 1968)
CRITTENDEN, C. C. (North Carolina Historical Commission) - 3 (1942, 1945)
CROSS, Joseph E. - 1 (Apr. 17, 1946)
CROSS, Lucy Manley - 1 (Aug. 10, 1948)
CROWELL, James W. (Pomona College) - 1 (Feb. 26, 1930)
CROWNOVER, Arthur, Jr. (Sons of the American Revolution) - 4 (1934, 1942)
CRUDUP, Josiah (Brenau College) - 2 (1947)
CRUIKSHANK, Earl Fee (Vanderbilt University, U.S. Army) - 20 (1932, 1933, 1939, 1942, 1944, 1945)
CRUMB, Frederick W. (Potsdam State Teachers College) - 2 (1948)
CULLOM and Ghertner Co. (A.S. Ghertner) - 4 (1937, 1948)
GUMMING, W. P. - 1 (n.d.)
CURL, R. F. (Methodist Church) - 1 (Mar. 15, 1944)
CURLEE, Abigail - 1 (Hay 26, 1940)
CURLEE, Joan - 7 (1954, 1956-58)
CURRENT, Richard h. (University of Illinois) - 2 (1953)
CURRY, Charlotte M. - 1 (June 12, 1922)
CURTI, Merle (University of Wisconsin) - 9 (1945, 1946, 1951, 1952)
CURTISS, W. M. (Foundation for Economic Education) - 1 (Jan. 19, 1953)
DALE, E. E. (University of Oklahoma) - 52 (1930, 1932, 1939, 1940, 1943-48, 1951, 1952, 1954, 1959, 1964, 1967)
DALE, William Pratt II - 1 (May 6, 1946)
DANIELS, Frances Clifton (Florida State University) - 8 (1948, 1951, 1854, 1958, 1959, 1961)
DANIELS, R. Balfour (University of Houston) - 1 (Sept. 27, 1965)
DANNALS, George C. - 1 (Nov. 18, 1940)
DAUGHERTY, W. D. (Hotel Savoy) - 1 (Nov. 6, 1936)
DAVENPORT, F. Garvin (Syracuse University, Transylvania College, Monmouth College) - 118 (1935-54, 1956-58)
DAVID, Henry (Queens College) - 2 (l948)
DAVIDSON, Philip (Agnes Scott College, Vanderbilt University, University of Louisville) - 20 (1941-43, 1948-51, 1960) (including 1 letter each from R.C. Cook and Godfrey Davies)
DAVIES, Godfrey (Huntington Library) - 1 (Nov. 13, 1952)
DAVIS, Charles Hall (Attorney at Law) - 2 (1944)
DAVIS, Charles S. (Florida State University) - 1 (Oct. 26, 1954)
DAVIS, Chester K. (New Mexico State University) - 1 (Jan. 16, 1963)
DAVIS, Edwin A. (Louisiana State University) - 11 (1942, 1944, 1949, 1950, 1953, 1958)
DAVIS, Frank (Sam Davis Hotel) - 1 (Oct. 20, 1936)
DAVIS, Gerald H. - 2 (1958)
DAVIS, J. Treadwell (Junior College of Augusta, Ga., Mississippi Southern College, University of Southern Mississippi) - 19 (1937, 1939-41, 1946, 1947, 1949-53, 1963, 1966)
DAVIS, Keith (University of Texas Library) - 2 (1939, n.d.)
DAVIS, Lambert (University of North Carolina Press) - 1 (Mar. 10, 1949)
DAVIS, Marjorie - 1 (July 13, 1937)
DAVIS, Mary Lamar - 1 (Sept. 15, 1940)
DAVIS, Robert E. (Texian Press) - 5 (1964, 1966, n.d.) (including 2 letters from W. Stull Holt)
DAVIS, Thurston (Colorado College) - 1 (Apr. 18, 1941)
DAY, James M. (Texas State Library) - 1 (Oct. 25, 1965)
DE TREVILLE, Catherine - 1 (Aug. 20, 1943)
DEAS, W. M. (First National Rank of Louisiana) - 1 (Sept. 2, 1932)
DEBIEN, G. - 3 (1945, 1947)
DELANEY, Sue Ellen - 1 (Jan. 29, 1942)
DELINAS, Rurand - 1 (Nov. 17, 1929)
DELZELL, Charles (and family) - 1 (Dec. 24, 1956)
DELLEN, Joseph E. (University of Maryland) - 1 (Sept. 30, 1957)
DEMIS, Frank S. - 1 (July 8, 1925)
DENMAN, Clarence P. (Western Kentucky State Teachers College) - 1 (Apr. 12, 1936)
DERHAM, Milo G. (University of Colorado) - l8 (1927-30, 1935, 1936)
DESCHAMPS, Margaret Burr (Coker College, Agnes Scott College) - 13 (1947-53)
DESTLER, Chester McA. (Southern Georgia Teachers College, Connecticut College) - 7 ( 1936, 1938, 1939, 1945, 1948, 1949)
DETWEILER, Philip F. (Journal of Southern History) - 19 (1954, 1957-59, 1963-65, n.d.) (including letters from Fred Cole, William Peery, and W. H. Stephenson)
DEWITT, John H. (Tennessee Court of Appeals) - 3 (including 1 from Cordell Hull) (1934-36)
DEWITT, Mrs. John H. (Tennessee Historical Commission) - 4 (1942, 1943)
DICK, Everett (Union College) - 6 (1938, 1939, 1943, 1949)
DIGKE^SOH,rQiiM.(Colorado State Teachers College) - 4 (1930, 1955)
DIEHL, Charles E. (Southern University Conference) - 1 (Nov. 4, 1946)
DIMICK, Howard T. - 5 (1945, 1949) (including 1 from Guy Stanton Ford)
DITMARS, R. Maud (Colorado Women's College) - 3 (1929)
DODD, T. Leo (Eldorado Township High School) - 1 (Jan. 30, 1942)
DODGE, John V. (Encyclopedia Britannica) - 1 (July 8, 1958)
DOLLAKHIDE, Louis E. - 1 (Aug. 16, 1945)
DONNALD, Morrill - 4 (1938, 1940)
DORMAN, Lewy - 15 (1931, 1933-35)
DORRANCE, Frances (Wyoming Historical and Genealogical Society) - 1 (Dec. 8, 1925)
DOWNES, Randolph C. (Smith College) - 1 (Jan. 30, 1946)
DOYLE, Clyde (U.S. Congress) - 3 (1924, 1925, 1949)
DOYLE, Joan (Louisiana State University Press) - 2 (1952, 1954)
DRIVER, Carl S. (Vanderbilt University) - 4 (1935, 1936) (including 3 from Mrs. Driver)
DRIVER, Lester - 1 (July 18, 1936)
DRUM, Emily - 1 (Sept. 14, 1960)
DUBOSE, Charles L. - 1 (Sept. 4, 1929)
DUGGAN, Laurence (U.S. Department of State) - 1 (Apr. 12, 1938)
DUKE, V. L. (University of Redlands) - 1 (June 1, 1920)
DUMOND, Dwight L. (University of Michigan, Mississippi Valley Historical Association) - 15 (1946, 1948, 1950, 1952, 1953, 1964, n.d.)
DUNIWAY, G. A. (Colorado College) - 13 (1921-23, 1925, 1929, n.d.)
DUNAGAN, W. 11.-1 (Feb. 6, 1950)
DUPLANTIS, Dorothy - 2 (1954)
DURKIN, Joseph T., S.J. (Georgetown University) - 1 (July 10, 1944)
DURRELL, L. W. (Colorado-Wyoming Academy of Science) - 1 (May 19, 1930)
DUTCH, Jim T. - 1 (Jan. 29, 1953)
DYER, Brainerd (University of California) - 2 (1949)
DYE, Sue (Indiana University) - 4 (1963-64)
DYER, J. P. (Florence State Teachers College, Vanderbilt University, South Georgia State College, Armstrong Junior College, Office of Price Administration, Tulane University) - 32 (1931-37. 1939, 1942, 1943, 1945, 1946, 1948, 1968) (including 3 from E. Merton Coulter, 1 from Thomas W. Gamble)
EASLEY, Georgia S. - 1 (Jan. 3, 1925)
EASTERBY, J. Ii. (College of Charleston, Historical Commission of South Carolina) - 2 (1946, 1949)
EASUM, C. V. (University of Wisconsin) - 2 (1948)
EATON, Clement (Lafayette College) - 1 (July 10, 1945)
EBLE, John (Eble Teachers Agency) - 1 (Feb. 20, 1939)
EBERLING, E. J. (Tennessee Division of Unemployment Compensation) - 1 (Aug. 5, 1938)
EBY, Frederick (University of Texas) - 5 (1921-23, 1927, 1929)
ECKER, Joseph T. (Middle Georgia College) - 1 (Mar. 2, 1936)
ECKHARDT, C. C. (University of Colorado) - 5 (1929, 1930, 1936)
EDMONDS, Katharine H.S. (Peninsula Enterprise) - 1 (Dec. 4, 1943)
EDWARDS, Robert L. (Harvard University) - 1 (Feb. 16, 1941)
EGGEN, H. O. (Class of '10A) - 1 (June 23, 1940)
EIDSON, John O. (University Center in Georgia) - 1 (Mar. 10, 1953)
ELLIOTT, Rush (Ohio University) - 1 (Dec. 29, 1959)
ELLIS, Elmer (University of Missouri) - 24 (1936, 1938-40, 1946, 1947, 1949, 1950, 1954) (including 1 each from John D. Hicks and Bell I. Wiley)
ELLIS, Milton (New England Quarterly) - 1 (June 26, 1943)
ELLISON, Joseph (Oregon State Agricultural College) - 1 (Mar. 4, 1931)
ELLISON, Martha L. (East Tennessee Historical Society) - 5 (1942, 1943)
ELLISON, Rhoda C. - 2 (1946)
EMMONS, Martha - 4 (1926, 1933) (including 1 from John M. Sharpe)
ENGLAND, J. Merton (Vanderbilt University, University of Kentucky, Journal of Southern History) - 21 (1939, 1941, 1943, 1945, 1947, 1950, 1952, 1955, 1956, 1961)
ENGLISH, W. Francis (University of Missouri) - 1 (Dec. 28, 1948)
ESTEP, Raymond (U.S. Air Force University) - 2 (1949, 1951)
EVANGELISTICA, Dominick - 1 (June 2, 1943)
EVANS, Alvin E. - 1 (Aug. 10, 1922)
EVANS, Luther H. (Library of Congress, Works Progress Administration) -11 (1936, 1937, 1942, 1945)
EVERETT, Donald E. (Tulane University) - 1 (May 28, 1953)
FARRIS, Hazel H. - 2 (1952)
FAW, W. W. (Tennessee Court of Appeals) - 1 (July 18, 1942)
FAWCETT, Ellen D. (Dictionary of American Biography) - 2 (1933)
FEINSTEIN, Estelle F. - see E. F. Fisher
FELGAR, Robert P. (Jacksonville State Teachers College) - 2 (1936)
FERGUSON, James S. - 1 (Feb. 2, 1950)
FERGUSON, John L. (Arkansas Historical Commission) - 1 (Nov. 2, 1965)
FIELD, Alston G. (Historical Records Survey) - 1 (May 6, 1936)
FIELDS, Eiflmett B., Jr. (Vanderbilt University) - 2 (1951, 1960)
FIERMAN, Floyd S. (Temple Mount Sinai) - 1 (Nov. 4, 1964)
FISHEL, Leslie H., Jr. (State Historical Society of Wisconsin) - 1 (Mar. 18, 1964)
FISHER, C. B. (Maryville College) - 1 (Dec. 20, 1945)
FISHER (FEINSTEIN), Estelle (University of Connecticut) - 11 (1944-47, 1949, 1963)
FISHWICK, Marshall W. (Yale University) - 1 (Mar. 5, 1948)
FITCH, Charles S. (United Press Associations) - 1 (Feb. 5, 1945)
FITE, Gilbert G. (University of Oklahoma) - 8 (1950, 1957, 1967)
FITE, Harley (Carson-Newman College) - 1 (May 19, 1964)
FITTS, Charles T. (Pomona College) - 1 (Sept. 11, 1933)
FLANDERS, Ralph B. (New York University) - 1 (July 3, 1944)
FLEETWOOD, Milton - 1 (Nov. 9, 1950)
FLEMING, D. F. (Vanderbilt University) - 2 (1931, 1938)
FLEMING, Doris A. (Vanderbilt University) - 1 (Sept. 28, 1953)
FLEMING, Eleanor - 1 (Aug. 15, 1935)
FLORIDA SPUR, The - 1 (Nov. 21, 1941)
FOLMSBEE, Stanley J. (East Tennessee Historical Society, University of Tennessee) - 12 (1937, 1942, 1943, 1945-^7) (including 1 from Robert H. White)
FOOTE, Alvin - 1 (Aug. 27, 1928)
FOOTE, Elsie Robins (Glenwood Springs Public Schools) - 1 (Nov. 28, 1927)
FORD, Guy Stanton (American Historical Association) - 5 (1942, 1945, 1946, 1951)
FRANKLIN PRESS, The - 44 (1942-49)
FRANKLIN, W. Neil (National Archives) - 8 (l943, 194, 1946, 1947)
FRANTZ, Joe B. (University of Texas) - 12 (1951, 1955, 1962-64, 1966) (including 1 each from H.H. Ransom, Dorman Winfrey, and Oliver W. Holmes)
FREELAND, William R. - 1 (Jan. 20, 1945)
FREEMAN, Mrs. P.R. - 1 (May 29, 1933)
FREIDEL, Frank (Navy Department) - 1 (July 26, 1946)
FRIEND, Llerena (University of Texas Library) - 2 (1951)
FRYE, Burton C. (Appleton-Century-Crofts) - 1 (Mar. 8, 1966)
FULLER, E. S. - 1 (June 1945)
FULLER, G. N. (Michigan Historical Commission) - 1 (1943, 1944)
FULLER, L. W. (University of Colorado, Colorado College) - 6 (1928-31, 1933)
FULLER, W. A. (University of Florida) - 10 (1924-26, 1928)
FULLER, Walter P. (The Floridian) - 1 (Dec. 27, 1944)
FULTON, Maurice G. - 1 (June 20, 1933)
FURR, Ray A. (Winthrop College) - 1 (Jan. 21, 1941)
FUTRELL, Robert Frank (Research Studies Institute, Air University) - 12 (1939, 1941-43, 1946, 1949, 1951, 1957, 1958)
GABRIEL, Ralph H. (American Historical Association) - 1 (n.d.)
GAGE, Lucy - 1 (Sept. 20, 1943)
GALLOWAY, Luida B. - 1 (June 20, 1949)
GAMBRELL, Herbert P. (Southern Methodist University, Dallas Historical Society, Philosophical Society of Texas) - 12 (1935, 1936, 1943, 1944, 1946-48, 1950, 1969) (including 1 from Sam Rayburn)
GANAWAY, Loomis Morton (Herbert Hoover Senior High School, San Diego Senior High School, San Diego Junior College) - l8 (1937-39, 1942, 1943, 1945, 1947, 1950, 1951, n.d.) (including 1 from Lansing B. Bloom)
GARLAND, J. L. - 2 (1947, 1948)
GARNER, Alfred W. (Mississippi State College) - 2 (1942)
GARRISON, Curtis W. (The Hayes Memorial) - 1 (May 2, 1939)
GARTH, T. R. - 2 (1922)
GATES, Paul W. (Cornell University) - 9 (1938, 1939, 1945, 1946, 1951, 1958) (including 1 to P.W.G. from Alfred B. Sears)
GEISER, S. W. (Southern Methodist University) - 1 (Oct. 2, 1947)
GEORGE, Dean - 3 (1944-46)
GERAGHTY, Michael J. - 2 (1958)
GEROULD, C. P. - 1 (May 19, 1924)
GESELL, Gerhard A. (Covington, Burling, Rublee, Acheson & Shorb) - 1 (Mar. 19, 1943)
GEWEHR, Wesley M. (University of Maryland) - 2 (1928, 1946)
GIBSON, William M. - 1 (Oct. 31, 1945)
GILBERT, Amy M. (Associated Colleges of Upper New York) - 1 (Mar. 21, 1947)
GILBERT, David H. (University of Texas Press) - 3 (1967)
GILES, Effie Dean - 1 (Mar. 4, 1941)
GILLIAM, Will D., Jr. (Journal of Southern History) - 2 (1956, 1957)
GILLILAND, C. V. (University of Southern California) - 1 (June 21, 1921)
GILMORE, Juliet - 4 (1955-56)
GILMORE, Robert J. (Colorado College) - 3 (1930)
GILMORE, Robert L. - 5 (1952, 1955, 1959, 1960)
GLENN, L. C. (Vanderbilt University) - 1 (June 18, 1930)
GOING, Allen (University of Houston) - 9 (1946, 1961, 1965, 1966)
GOODELL, Robert C. (Washington and Lee University) - 2 (1942)
GOODING, Lydia (Columbia University) - 1 (Nov. 13, 1943)
G00DLOE, Hallum W. (Tennessee Department of Banking) - 5 (1942)
GOODWIN, Cardinal (Mills College) - 16 (1921, 1931-33, 1942)
GOODYKOONTZ, Colin B. (University of Colorado) - 7 (1937, 194. 1946, 1949)
GORE, Albert (Tennessee Department of Labor, U.S. Congress) - 2 (1937, 1943)
GOTTSCHALK, Louis (University of Chicago) - 4 (1953)
GOVAN, Jane - 2 (1956, n.d.)
GCVAN, Thomas P. (Emory University, University of the South, National
Council of the Protestant Episcopal Church) - 41 (1935, 1937-^, 1946, 1947, 1950, 1952-56, 1959)
GRAHAM, Emmette V. (Associated Advertising Company) - 8 (1927, 1933)
GRANT, C. L. (Georgia State College) - 5 (1954, 1957, 1960, 1961)
GRANT, U. S., 3rd. (National Council for Historic Sites and Buildings) -1 (Dec. 13, 1949)
GRANTHAM, Dewey W., Jr. (Vanderbilt University) - 17 (1947, 1948, 1953-61)
GRAY, Wood (George Washington University) - 3 (l946, 1950, 1955)
GREEN, Fletcher M. (Emory University, University of North Carolina, Southern Historical Association) - 38 (1935-37, 1939, 1943-46, 1948-51, 1953, 1958, 1961)
GREENE, Helen (Georgia State College for Women) - 1 (1947)
GREENFIELD, Kent Roberts (Johns Hopkins University, Department of the Army) - 3 (1940, 1950)
GREGORY, E. W., Jr. - 1 (Mar. 14, 1932)
GREGORY, W. Edgar (Delta Alpha Phi Fraternity) - 1 (June 1, 1932)
GREICUS, Elizabeth - 6 (1956, 1959, 1964)
GREER, James K. (Howard College) - 3 (1934, 1935, 1943)
GRESHAM, L. P. (Trevecca Nazarene College) - 1 (Oct. 29, 1952)
GRESSLEY, Gene M. (University of Wyoming) - 2 (1958)
GRIFFIN, Richard W. III (The 1946 Howler) - 1 (July 20, 1948)
GRIFFITH, R. H. - 1 (May 28, 1933)
GRIFFITH, R. W. (Mississippi Heights Academy) - 1 (Feb 16, 1931)
GRIFFITH, William J. - 6 (1964, n.d.)
GRIMES, Irvin L. - 1 (Apr. 5, 1961)
GRIMM, Harold J. (Indiana University) - 1 (Jan. 15, 1958)
GRINNELL, Leslie (Macmillan Company) - 2 (1943)
GUERRY, Alex (University of the South) - 3 (1932, 1933, 1941)
GRISE, F. G. (Western Kentucky State Teachers College) - 2 (1932)
GUSTAVSON, Carl (Miami University) - 1 (Apr. 19, 1945)
GUTSCH, Milton R. (University of Texas) - 37 (1920, 1925-28, 1930, 1931, 1933, 1935-41, 1950, 1951)
GUYTON, David E. (Blue Mountain College) -
HACKETT, Charles W. (University of Texas) - 22 (1927, 1929, 1931, 1932, 1937, 1938, n.d.)
HACKETT, J. F. (Tulane University) - 1 (Sept. 13, 1949)
HAFEN, LeKoy R. (State Historical... Society of Colorado) - 7 (1924, 1926, 1927, 1930, 1945)
HAGEN, Olftf T. (U.S. Department of the Interior) - 1 (Sept. 13, 1933)
HAINES, C. G. (University of Texas) - 15 (1920-23, 1925)
HALL, Mary Jean - 1 (Apr. 5, 1950)
HALL, Wilmer L. (Virginia State Library) - 1 (Apr. 25, 1946)
HAMER, Marcelle Lively (University of Texas Library) (1937, 1938, 1940, 1941, 1949)
IIAMER, Marguerite B. (University of Tennessee) - 1 (Feb. 24, 1931)